[{"subjectID":"w4bjxpb54v","prolificID":"6736017e076d3440b572571d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774211dbe7f4645d4f66089","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664505678,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"238","question":"Did you commute to work today and if so, was there traffic? Was it better or worse than usual?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":31439,"timeElapsed":138526},{"subjectID":"w4bjxpb54v","prolificID":"6736017e076d3440b572571d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774211dbe7f4645d4f66089","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664549453,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"238","question":"Did you commute to work today and if so, was there traffic? Was it better or worse than usual?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":43774,"timeElapsed":182302},{"subjectID":"w4bjxpb54v","prolificID":"6736017e076d3440b572571d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774211dbe7f4645d4f66089","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664566497,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"238","question":"Did you commute to work today and if so, was there traffic? Was it better or worse than usual?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":17042,"timeElapsed":199346},{"subjectID":"w4bjxpb54v","prolificID":"6736017e076d3440b572571d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774211dbe7f4645d4f66089","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664584867,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"238","question":"Did you commute to work today and if so, was there traffic? Was it better or worse than usual?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":18368,"timeElapsed":217716},{"subjectID":"w4bjxpb54v","prolificID":"6736017e076d3440b572571d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774211dbe7f4645d4f66089","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664597033,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"238","question":"Did you commute to work today and if so, was there traffic? Was it better or worse than usual?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":3,"rt":12164,"timeElapsed":229882},{"subjectID":"w4bjxpb54v","prolificID":"6736017e076d3440b572571d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774211dbe7f4645d4f66089","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664605308,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"238","question":"Did you commute to work today and if so, was there traffic? Was it better or worse than usual?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":8275,"timeElapsed":238157},{"subjectID":"w4bjxpb54v","prolificID":"6736017e076d3440b572571d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774211dbe7f4645d4f66089","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664610633,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"238","question":"Did you commute to work today and if so, was there traffic? Was it better or worse than usual?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":5323,"timeElapsed":243482},{"subjectID":"w4bjxpb54v","prolificID":"6736017e076d3440b572571d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774211dbe7f4645d4f66089","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664655170,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"238","question":"Did you commute to work today and if so, was there traffic? Was it better or worse than usual?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":44536,"timeElapsed":288019},{"subjectID":"w4bjxpb54v","prolificID":"6736017e076d3440b572571d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774211dbe7f4645d4f66089","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664670004,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"238","question":"Did you commute to work today and if so, was there traffic? Was it better or worse than usual?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":14832,"timeElapsed":302853},{"subjectID":"w4bjxpb54v","prolificID":"6736017e076d3440b572571d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774211dbe7f4645d4f66089","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664692158,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"99","question":"Under what circumstances do you think you could kill someone, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":20095,"timeElapsed":325007},{"subjectID":"w4bjxpb54v","prolificID":"6736017e076d3440b572571d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774211dbe7f4645d4f66089","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664699778,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"99","question":"Under what circumstances do you think you could kill someone, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":7619,"timeElapsed":332627},{"subjectID":"w4bjxpb54v","prolificID":"6736017e076d3440b572571d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774211dbe7f4645d4f66089","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664714548,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"99","question":"Under what circumstances do you think you could kill someone, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":96,"rt":14768,"timeElapsed":347397},{"subjectID":"w4bjxpb54v","prolificID":"6736017e076d3440b572571d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774211dbe7f4645d4f66089","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664725504,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"99","question":"Under what circumstances do you think you could kill someone, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":25,"rt":10955,"timeElapsed":358353},{"subjectID":"w4bjxpb54v","prolificID":"6736017e076d3440b572571d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774211dbe7f4645d4f66089","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664730904,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"99","question":"Under what circumstances do you think you could kill someone, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":5399,"timeElapsed":363753},{"subjectID":"w4bjxpb54v","prolificID":"6736017e076d3440b572571d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774211dbe7f4645d4f66089","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664734448,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"99","question":"Under what circumstances do you think you could kill someone, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3543,"timeElapsed":367297},{"subjectID":"w4bjxpb54v","prolificID":"6736017e076d3440b572571d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774211dbe7f4645d4f66089","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664741566,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"99","question":"Under what circumstances do you think you could kill someone, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":7117,"timeElapsed":374415},{"subjectID":"w4bjxpb54v","prolificID":"6736017e076d3440b572571d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774211dbe7f4645d4f66089","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664750386,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"99","question":"Under what circumstances do you think you could kill someone, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":8818,"timeElapsed":383234},{"subjectID":"w4bjxpb54v","prolificID":"6736017e076d3440b572571d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774211dbe7f4645d4f66089","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664755637,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"99","question":"Under what circumstances do you think you could kill someone, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":5251,"timeElapsed":388486},{"subjectID":"w4bjxpb54v","prolificID":"6736017e076d3440b572571d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774211dbe7f4645d4f66089","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664770876,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"141","question":"What is the best restaurant you have been to in the last month? Describe your experience.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":13681,"timeElapsed":403724},{"subjectID":"w4bjxpb54v","prolificID":"6736017e076d3440b572571d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774211dbe7f4645d4f66089","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664776043,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"141","question":"What is the best restaurant you have been to in the last month? Describe your experience.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":5167,"timeElapsed":408892},{"subjectID":"w4bjxpb54v","prolificID":"6736017e076d3440b572571d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774211dbe7f4645d4f66089","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664785025,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"141","question":"What is the best restaurant you have been to in the last month? Describe your experience.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":8981,"timeElapsed":417874},{"subjectID":"w4bjxpb54v","prolificID":"6736017e076d3440b572571d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774211dbe7f4645d4f66089","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664799333,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"141","question":"What is the best restaurant you have been to in the last month? Describe your experience.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":14307,"timeElapsed":432182},{"subjectID":"w4bjxpb54v","prolificID":"6736017e076d3440b572571d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774211dbe7f4645d4f66089","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664808617,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"141","question":"What is the best restaurant you have been to in the last month? Describe your experience.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":9283,"timeElapsed":441466},{"subjectID":"w4bjxpb54v","prolificID":"6736017e076d3440b572571d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774211dbe7f4645d4f66089","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664813211,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"141","question":"What is the best restaurant you have been to in the last month? Describe your experience.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":4593,"timeElapsed":446060},{"subjectID":"w4bjxpb54v","prolificID":"6736017e076d3440b572571d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774211dbe7f4645d4f66089","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664821499,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"141","question":"What is the best restaurant you have been to in the last month? Describe your experience.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":8287,"timeElapsed":454348},{"subjectID":"w4bjxpb54v","prolificID":"6736017e076d3440b572571d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774211dbe7f4645d4f66089","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664830165,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"141","question":"What is the best restaurant you have been to in the last month? Describe your experience.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":8665,"timeElapsed":463014},{"subjectID":"w4bjxpb54v","prolificID":"6736017e076d3440b572571d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774211dbe7f4645d4f66089","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664835299,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"141","question":"What is the best restaurant you have been to in the last month? Describe your experience.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":5133,"timeElapsed":468148},{"subjectID":"w4bjxpb54v","prolificID":"6736017e076d3440b572571d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774211dbe7f4645d4f66089","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664846389,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"1","question":"Given the choice of anyone in the world (alive or dead), whom would you want as a dinner guest?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":9899,"timeElapsed":479238},{"subjectID":"w4bjxpb54v","prolificID":"6736017e076d3440b572571d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774211dbe7f4645d4f66089","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664852335,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"1","question":"Given the choice of anyone in the world (alive or dead), whom would you want as a dinner guest?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":5945,"timeElapsed":485184},{"subjectID":"w4bjxpb54v","prolificID":"6736017e076d3440b572571d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774211dbe7f4645d4f66089","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664859939,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"1","question":"Given the choice of anyone in the world (alive or dead), whom would you want as a dinner guest?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":7603,"timeElapsed":492788},{"subjectID":"w4bjxpb54v","prolificID":"6736017e076d3440b572571d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774211dbe7f4645d4f66089","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664876371,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"1","question":"Given the choice of anyone in the world (alive or dead), whom would you want as a dinner guest?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":16431,"timeElapsed":509220},{"subjectID":"w4bjxpb54v","prolificID":"6736017e076d3440b572571d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774211dbe7f4645d4f66089","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664887137,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"1","question":"Given the choice of anyone in the world (alive or dead), whom would you want as a dinner guest?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":10765,"timeElapsed":519986},{"subjectID":"w4bjxpb54v","prolificID":"6736017e076d3440b572571d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774211dbe7f4645d4f66089","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664890354,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"1","question":"Given the choice of anyone in the world (alive or dead), whom would you want as a dinner guest?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":3217,"timeElapsed":523203},{"subjectID":"w4bjxpb54v","prolificID":"6736017e076d3440b572571d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774211dbe7f4645d4f66089","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664893683,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"1","question":"Given the choice of anyone in the world (alive or dead), whom would you want as a dinner guest?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":3327,"timeElapsed":526532},{"subjectID":"w4bjxpb54v","prolificID":"6736017e076d3440b572571d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774211dbe7f4645d4f66089","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664899655,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"1","question":"Given the choice of anyone in the world (alive or dead), whom would you want as a dinner guest?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":5971,"timeElapsed":532504},{"subjectID":"w4bjxpb54v","prolificID":"6736017e076d3440b572571d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774211dbe7f4645d4f66089","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664903294,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"1","question":"Given the choice of anyone in the world (alive or dead), whom would you want as a dinner guest?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3639,"timeElapsed":536143},{"subjectID":"w4bjxpb54v","prolificID":"6736017e076d3440b572571d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774211dbe7f4645d4f66089","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664920730,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"236","question":"Choose one item of clothing you are currently wearing and describe how you came to own this item.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":16271,"timeElapsed":553579},{"subjectID":"w4bjxpb54v","prolificID":"6736017e076d3440b572571d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774211dbe7f4645d4f66089","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664932696,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"236","question":"Choose one item of clothing you are currently wearing and describe how you came to own this item.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":11965,"timeElapsed":565545},{"subjectID":"w4bjxpb54v","prolificID":"6736017e076d3440b572571d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774211dbe7f4645d4f66089","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664938600,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"236","question":"Choose one item of clothing you are currently wearing and describe how you came to own this item.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":5903,"timeElapsed":571449},{"subjectID":"w4bjxpb54v","prolificID":"6736017e076d3440b572571d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774211dbe7f4645d4f66089","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664943468,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"236","question":"Choose one item of clothing you are currently wearing and describe how you came to own this item.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":4867,"timeElapsed":576317},{"subjectID":"w4bjxpb54v","prolificID":"6736017e076d3440b572571d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774211dbe7f4645d4f66089","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664950640,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"236","question":"Choose one item of clothing you are currently wearing and describe how you came to own this item.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":7171,"timeElapsed":583489},{"subjectID":"w4bjxpb54v","prolificID":"6736017e076d3440b572571d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774211dbe7f4645d4f66089","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664957003,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"236","question":"Choose one item of clothing you are currently wearing and describe how you came to own this item.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":6361,"timeElapsed":589852},{"subjectID":"w4bjxpb54v","prolificID":"6736017e076d3440b572571d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774211dbe7f4645d4f66089","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664962058,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"236","question":"Choose one item of clothing you are currently wearing and describe how you came to own this item.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":5054,"timeElapsed":594907},{"subjectID":"w4bjxpb54v","prolificID":"6736017e076d3440b572571d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774211dbe7f4645d4f66089","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664983962,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"236","question":"Choose one item of clothing you are currently wearing and describe how you came to own this item.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":21903,"timeElapsed":616811},{"subjectID":"w4bjxpb54v","prolificID":"6736017e076d3440b572571d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774211dbe7f4645d4f66089","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664987866,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"236","question":"Choose one item of clothing you are currently wearing and describe how you came to own this item.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":3903,"timeElapsed":620715},{"subjectID":"w4bjxpb54v","prolificID":"6736017e076d3440b572571d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774211dbe7f4645d4f66089","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665004138,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":15027,"timeElapsed":636987},{"subjectID":"w4bjxpb54v","prolificID":"6736017e076d3440b572571d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774211dbe7f4645d4f66089","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665008836,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":4697,"timeElapsed":641685},{"subjectID":"w4bjxpb54v","prolificID":"6736017e076d3440b572571d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774211dbe7f4645d4f66089","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665017714,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":8877,"timeElapsed":650563},{"subjectID":"w4bjxpb54v","prolificID":"6736017e076d3440b572571d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774211dbe7f4645d4f66089","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665022132,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":4417,"timeElapsed":654981},{"subjectID":"w4bjxpb54v","prolificID":"6736017e076d3440b572571d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774211dbe7f4645d4f66089","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665028232,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":6099,"timeElapsed":661081},{"subjectID":"w4bjxpb54v","prolificID":"6736017e076d3440b572571d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774211dbe7f4645d4f66089","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665034372,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":6139,"timeElapsed":667221},{"subjectID":"w4bjxpb54v","prolificID":"6736017e076d3440b572571d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774211dbe7f4645d4f66089","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665043942,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":9569,"timeElapsed":676791},{"subjectID":"w4bjxpb54v","prolificID":"6736017e076d3440b572571d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774211dbe7f4645d4f66089","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665049742,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":5799,"timeElapsed":682590},{"subjectID":"w4bjxpb54v","prolificID":"6736017e076d3440b572571d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774211dbe7f4645d4f66089","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665058228,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":8485,"timeElapsed":691076},{"subjectID":"w4bjxpb54v","prolificID":"6736017e076d3440b572571d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774211dbe7f4645d4f66089","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665063729,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":5501,"timeElapsed":696578},{"subjectID":"w4bjxpb54v","prolificID":"6736017e076d3440b572571d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774211dbe7f4645d4f66089","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665074165,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"216","question":"Do you have a bedtime routine? What do you typically do to fall asleep?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":9287,"timeElapsed":707014},{"subjectID":"w4bjxpb54v","prolificID":"6736017e076d3440b572571d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774211dbe7f4645d4f66089","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665077693,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"216","question":"Do you have a bedtime routine? What do you typically do to fall asleep?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3527,"timeElapsed":710542},{"subjectID":"w4bjxpb54v","prolificID":"6736017e076d3440b572571d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774211dbe7f4645d4f66089","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665083371,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"216","question":"Do you have a bedtime routine? What do you typically do to fall asleep?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":5677,"timeElapsed":716220},{"subjectID":"w4bjxpb54v","prolificID":"6736017e076d3440b572571d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774211dbe7f4645d4f66089","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665088429,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"216","question":"Do you have a bedtime routine? What do you typically do to fall asleep?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":5057,"timeElapsed":721278},{"subjectID":"w4bjxpb54v","prolificID":"6736017e076d3440b572571d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774211dbe7f4645d4f66089","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665091901,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"216","question":"Do you have a bedtime routine? What do you typically do to fall asleep?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3471,"timeElapsed":724750},{"subjectID":"w4bjxpb54v","prolificID":"6736017e076d3440b572571d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774211dbe7f4645d4f66089","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665096057,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"216","question":"Do you have a bedtime routine? What do you typically do to fall asleep?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":4155,"timeElapsed":728906},{"subjectID":"w4bjxpb54v","prolificID":"6736017e076d3440b572571d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774211dbe7f4645d4f66089","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665099503,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"216","question":"Do you have a bedtime routine? What do you typically do to fall asleep?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3445,"timeElapsed":732352},{"subjectID":"w4bjxpb54v","prolificID":"6736017e076d3440b572571d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774211dbe7f4645d4f66089","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665105101,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"216","question":"Do you have a bedtime routine? What do you typically do to fall asleep?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":5596,"timeElapsed":737950},{"subjectID":"w4bjxpb54v","prolificID":"6736017e076d3440b572571d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774211dbe7f4645d4f66089","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665108699,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"216","question":"Do you have a bedtime routine? What do you typically do to fall asleep?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3597,"timeElapsed":741548},{"subjectID":"w4bjxpb54v","prolificID":"6736017e076d3440b572571d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774211dbe7f4645d4f66089","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665117115,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"73","question":"What’s something you believe in that other people close to you do not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":7241,"timeElapsed":749964},{"subjectID":"w4bjxpb54v","prolificID":"6736017e076d3440b572571d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774211dbe7f4645d4f66089","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665119935,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"73","question":"What’s something you believe in that other people close to you do not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2819,"timeElapsed":752784},{"subjectID":"w4bjxpb54v","prolificID":"6736017e076d3440b572571d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774211dbe7f4645d4f66089","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665126929,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"73","question":"What’s something you believe in that other people close to you do not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":6993,"timeElapsed":759778},{"subjectID":"w4bjxpb54v","prolificID":"6736017e076d3440b572571d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774211dbe7f4645d4f66089","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665129831,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"73","question":"What’s something you believe in that other people close to you do not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":2901,"timeElapsed":762680},{"subjectID":"w4bjxpb54v","prolificID":"6736017e076d3440b572571d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774211dbe7f4645d4f66089","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665135957,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"73","question":"What’s something you believe in that other people close to you do not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":6125,"timeElapsed":768806},{"subjectID":"w4bjxpb54v","prolificID":"6736017e076d3440b572571d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774211dbe7f4645d4f66089","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665141607,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What’s something you believe in that other people close to you do not?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":5649,"timeElapsed":774456},{"subjectID":"w4bjxpb54v","prolificID":"6736017e076d3440b572571d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774211dbe7f4645d4f66089","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665146707,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"73","question":"What’s something you believe in that other people close to you do not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":5099,"timeElapsed":779556},{"subjectID":"w4bjxpb54v","prolificID":"6736017e076d3440b572571d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774211dbe7f4645d4f66089","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665150303,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"73","question":"What’s something you believe in that other people close to you do not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3595,"timeElapsed":783152},{"subjectID":"w4bjxpb54v","prolificID":"6736017e076d3440b572571d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774211dbe7f4645d4f66089","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665158275,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"73","question":"What’s something you believe in that other people close to you do not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":7971,"timeElapsed":791124},{"subjectID":"w4bjxpb54v","prolificID":"6736017e076d3440b572571d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774211dbe7f4645d4f66089","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665162433,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"73","question":"What’s something you believe in that other people close to you do not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4157,"timeElapsed":795282},{"subjectID":"w4bjxpb54v","prolificID":"6736017e076d3440b572571d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774211dbe7f4645d4f66089","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665174233,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"97","question":"What is the first thing you hope people notice about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":10741,"timeElapsed":807082},{"subjectID":"w4bjxpb54v","prolificID":"6736017e076d3440b572571d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774211dbe7f4645d4f66089","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665177583,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"97","question":"What is the first thing you hope people notice about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":3349,"timeElapsed":810432},{"subjectID":"w4bjxpb54v","prolificID":"6736017e076d3440b572571d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774211dbe7f4645d4f66089","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665184587,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"97","question":"What is the first thing you hope people notice about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":7003,"timeElapsed":817436},{"subjectID":"w4bjxpb54v","prolificID":"6736017e076d3440b572571d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774211dbe7f4645d4f66089","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665187673,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"97","question":"What is the first thing you hope people notice about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":3085,"timeElapsed":820522},{"subjectID":"w4bjxpb54v","prolificID":"6736017e076d3440b572571d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774211dbe7f4645d4f66089","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665191597,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"97","question":"What is the first thing you hope people notice about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":3923,"timeElapsed":824446},{"subjectID":"w4bjxpb54v","prolificID":"6736017e076d3440b572571d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774211dbe7f4645d4f66089","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665194459,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"97","question":"What is the first thing you hope people notice about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":2861,"timeElapsed":827308},{"subjectID":"w4bjxpb54v","prolificID":"6736017e076d3440b572571d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774211dbe7f4645d4f66089","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665198559,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"97","question":"What is the first thing you hope people notice about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":4099,"timeElapsed":831407},{"subjectID":"w4bjxpb54v","prolificID":"6736017e076d3440b572571d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774211dbe7f4645d4f66089","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665205193,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"97","question":"What is the first thing you hope people notice about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":6633,"timeElapsed":838042},{"subjectID":"w4bjxpb54v","prolificID":"6736017e076d3440b572571d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774211dbe7f4645d4f66089","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665207771,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"97","question":"What is the first thing you hope people notice about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":2577,"timeElapsed":840619},{"subjectID":"w4bjxpb54v","prolificID":"6736017e076d3440b572571d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774211dbe7f4645d4f66089","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665216388,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"16","question":"What do you value most in a friendship?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":7447,"timeElapsed":849237},{"subjectID":"w4bjxpb54v","prolificID":"6736017e076d3440b572571d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774211dbe7f4645d4f66089","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665219397,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"16","question":"What do you value most in a friendship?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3007,"timeElapsed":852246},{"subjectID":"w4bjxpb54v","prolificID":"6736017e076d3440b572571d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774211dbe7f4645d4f66089","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665224822,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"16","question":"What do you value most in a friendship?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":5424,"timeElapsed":857671},{"subjectID":"w4bjxpb54v","prolificID":"6736017e076d3440b572571d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774211dbe7f4645d4f66089","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665227694,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"16","question":"What do you value most in a friendship?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":2871,"timeElapsed":860543},{"subjectID":"w4bjxpb54v","prolificID":"6736017e076d3440b572571d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774211dbe7f4645d4f66089","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665236056,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"16","question":"What do you value most in a friendship?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":8361,"timeElapsed":868905},{"subjectID":"w4bjxpb54v","prolificID":"6736017e076d3440b572571d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774211dbe7f4645d4f66089","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665238698,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"16","question":"What do you value most in a friendship?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":2641,"timeElapsed":871547},{"subjectID":"w4bjxpb54v","prolificID":"6736017e076d3440b572571d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774211dbe7f4645d4f66089","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665241846,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"16","question":"What do you value most in a friendship?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3147,"timeElapsed":874695},{"subjectID":"w4bjxpb54v","prolificID":"6736017e076d3440b572571d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774211dbe7f4645d4f66089","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665246732,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"16","question":"What do you value most in a friendship?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4885,"timeElapsed":879581},{"subjectID":"w4bjxpb54v","prolificID":"6736017e076d3440b572571d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774211dbe7f4645d4f66089","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665249086,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"16","question":"What do you value most in a friendship?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2353,"timeElapsed":881935}]